<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<object>
  <name>Plans</name>
  <date>13/09/2010 17:27:05</date>
  <code>626771ad-83b4-4ae6-aff9-dc24f2620669</code>
  <legend-item></legend-item>
  <field isInDescriptor="true">
    <code>018fa1bd-056e-443a-86c6-c974b12fd952</code>
    <name>Name</name>
    <type>text</type>
    <style>InputText</style>
  </field>
  <field isInDescriptor="true">
    <code>c4b1382a-387f-4aae-89e6-7fa8941ecd63</code>
    <name>Price</name>
    <type>text</type>
    <style>InputText</style>
  </field>
  <field isInDescriptor="false">
    <code>caf7fcc9-989b-437f-8ffa-0b6ddbf3f999</code>
    <name>Summary</name>
    <type>text</type>
    <style>InputText</style>
  </field>
  <field isInDescriptor="false">
    <code>9c579b46-ab64-4cbd-804f-82ea9b7ad38e</code>
    <name>Description</name>
    <type>text</type>
    <style>InputText</style>
  </field>
  <listInstances>
    <instance>
      <instanceAttValue>
        <field>Name</field>
        <value>Evacuation</value>
      </instanceAttValue>
      <instanceAttValue>
        <field>Price</field>
        <value>150</value>
      </instanceAttValue>
      <instanceAttValue>
        <field>Summary</field>
        <value>For a range of health screenings, vaccinations, dental and optical treatment</value>
      </instanceAttValue>
      <instanceAttValue>
        <field>Description</field>
        <value>For when you can't get the treatment you need in a local hospital.The Worldwide Evacuation option covers you for reasonable transport costs to the nearest suitable medical centre, when the treatment you need is not available nearby. Repatriation, which is also included, gives you the added option of returning to your home country or specified country of nationality, to be treated in familiar surroundings.</value>
      </instanceAttValue>
    </instance>
    <instance>
      <instanceAttValue>
        <field>Name</field>
        <value>Medical Insurance</value>
      </instanceAttValue>
      <instanceAttValue>
        <field>Price</field>
        <value>100</value>
      </instanceAttValue>
      <instanceAttValue>
        <field>Summary</field>
        <value>For hospital treatment and overnight stays, plus related benefits</value>
      </instanceAttValue>
      <instanceAttValue>
        <field>Description</field>
        <value>For treatment received whilst staying in hospital, either overnight or as a day-case Worldwide Medical Insurance gives you the reassurance of covering essential hospital treatment you may need, whether in an emergency or a planned visit. All surgery, cancer treatment and advanced imaging, whether received whilst staying in hospital or as a visiting patient, are also included. You may have chosen this cover on its own, or together with any combination of our options.</value>
      </instanceAttValue>
    </instance>
    <instance>
      <instanceAttValue>
        <field>Name</field>
        <value>Medical Plus</value>
      </instanceAttValue>
      <instanceAttValue>
        <field>Price</field>
        <value>50</value>
      </instanceAttValue>
      <instanceAttValue>
        <field>Summary</field>
        <value>For specialist treatment when you do not need to stay in hospital.</value>
      </instanceAttValue>
      <instanceAttValue>
        <field>Description</field>
        <value>Worldwide Medical Plus covers you for consultations with a doctor or specialist and medical treatments that do not require a hospital stay. These may include osteopathy or complementary therapies, for example. Some of these treatments or consultations may take place before or after a hospital stay, but many will be totally independent.</value>
      </instanceAttValue>
    </instance>
    <instance>
      <instanceAttValue>
        <field>Name</field>
        <value>Medicines and Equipment</value>
      </instanceAttValue>
      <instanceAttValue>
        <field>Price</field>
        <value>130</value>
      </instanceAttValue>
      <instanceAttValue>
        <field>Summary</field>
        <value>For prescribed medicines and medical equipment</value>
      </instanceAttValue>
      <instanceAttValue>
        <field>Description</field>
        <value>For prescribed medicines and medical equipment. Often, treatment doesn't end when you leave the hospital or clinic or after you have seen a specialist. This option covers you for prescription medicines and the rental of medical appliances, such as oxygen supplies or wheelchairs. Our unique benefit for long-term prescriptions will also pay for any medicine required to manage chronic conditions such as asthma.</value>
      </instanceAttValue>
    </instance>
  </listInstances>
</object>

